SHUBHAM RAJ LAXMI

ENGINEERING STUDENT



CONTACT



+91-980 114 7064



shubhamrajlaxmi282@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/



shubham-raj-laxmi

PROJECTS

- Diabetes Detection
- website on system backup software

PROFILE

I am a pre-final year under-graduating engineering student from DIT University, Dehradun. I am pursuing my Bachelor of Technology degree in the field of computer science and engineering with a specialization in Cloud Computing and Virtualisation. I am very much interested in web designing and development also.

EDUCATION

PRE-FINAL UNDER-GRADUATION

ACADEMIC YEAR | 2017 - 2021

HIGH SCHOOL

ACADEMIC YEAR | 2014 - 2016

SECONDARY SCHOOL

ACADEMIC YEAR | 2014

COUSEWORK

IBM Watson, IBM Cloud, object oriented software engineering, operating system, computer architecture, DBMS, compiler design, theory of computation, computer graphics, digital image processing, artificial intelligence, pattern recognition using AI, discrete mathematics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPMENT

APTRON (NOIDA) JUNE 2019 - AUG 2019

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR MY CAPTAIN (JAN 2020-FEB 2020)

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR CODING NINJAS (MARCH 2020- CONTINUED)

WORKSHOPS AND SEMINARS

- PCB DESIGNING
- WATSON
- WEB ESIGNING
- WEB DEVELOPMENT
- INTRODUCTION TO MACHINE LEARNING
- INTRODUCTION TO GRAPHIC DESIGN

OTHER SKILLS

- CONTENT WRITING
- CREATIVE WRITING
- PUBLIC SPEAKING
- MANAGEMENT SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

- ENGLISH
- HINDI

COMPUTER SKILLS

• PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C, C++, PYTHON, Fundamentals of C#, Fundamentals of Java.

• SOFTWARES/PLATFORMS

Notepad++, Node JS, Watson, Slack

• OPERATING SYATEM

WINDOWS

• TOOLS

HTML 5. CSS 3. Bootstrap

SERVERS

WAMP AND XAMP SERVERS, C PANEL, PHP

CERTIFICATES AND MOOCS

• PCB DESIGNING

UPES DEHRADUN | April 2018

WEB DESIGNING

Dit University | February 2018

• WEB DEVELOPMENT

APTRON | August 2019

• INTRODUCTION TO DATA SCIENCE

IBM (Courseera) | April 2020

• DATA STRUCTURES USING PYTHON

University of Michigan (Courseera) | April 2020

PYTHON

University of Michigan (Courseera) | March 2020

HTML 5

University of Michigan (Courseera) | April 2020

• PYTHON FOR WEB ACCESS

University of Michigan (Courseera) | May 2020

ACHIVEMENTS

SCHOOL ACHIVEMENTS

JUNIOR SCHOOL CAPTAIN(COTTAGES, VICE CAPTAIN (HOUSES IN SCHOOL, HEAD ASSEMBLY COORDINATOR, HEAD VOLUNTEERING COORDINATOR, MANAGEMENT HEAD, DEPUTY COORDINATOR OF CU-CURRICULUM ACTIVITIES

- DEPUTY TECHNICAL HEAD (COLLEGE FEST YOUTHOPIA)
- MEMBER OF ORGANISING COMMITTEE (YOUTHPIA)
- PRESIDENT OF A TECHNICAL CLUB (DIT IMPULSE)
- MANAGEMENT HEAD OF TECHNICAL CLUB (DIT IMPULSE)
- DEPUTY HR OF A TECHNICAL CLUB (HACKTELLIGENCE)